let quiz=[
    {
      question: "Which number is odd one out -> 9678, 4572, 5261, 3527, 6895, 7768 :",
      option: [
           "4572",
           "3527",
           "9678",
           "7768",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What is 35% of 150 :",
      option: [
           "52.5",
           "62.5",
           "72.5",
           "82.5",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What number should replace the question mark -> 16, 23, 19, 19, 22, 15, 25, ? :",
      option: [
           "18",
           "11",
           "17",
           "10",
      ],
       answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What two numbers should replace the question mark -> 0, 1, 2, 5, 20, 25, ?, ? :",
      option: [
           "123, 135",
           "150, 157",
           "120, 109",
           "39, 182",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What number should replace the question mark -> 1, 101, 15, 4, 29, -93, 43, -190, ? :",
      option: [
           "57",
           "43",
           "34",
           "75",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Can you find the the missing number -> 19, 11, 11, ?, 12 :",
      option: [
           "8",
           "9",
           "5",
           "2",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "What is the weight of A ? A+A=120kg , B+A=70kg, A+B+C=90kg :",
      option: [
           "22",
           "30",
           "50",
           "20",
      ],
      answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Find the value of '?' in the sequence -> 1+4=5, 2+5=12, 3+6=21, 8+11=? :",
      option: [
           "96",
           "69",
           "36",
           "63",
      ],
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What number should replace the question mark -> A+B=76, A-B=38, A/B=? :",
      option: [
           "2",
           "3",
           "5",
           "4",
      ],
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Which 4-digit number multiplied by 4 gives the same number in reverse-> that is abcd*4=dcba",
      option: [
           "8712",
           "3421",
           "2178",
           "8713",
      ],
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
  question: "Look at the series : 2 , 1, (1/2) , (1/4) , ..... what number should come next ?",
  option: [
  "(1/3)",
  "(1/8)",
  "(2/8)",
  "(1/16)",
  ],
  answer: 2, 
},
{
  question: "Look at the series : 7 , 10 , 8 , 11 , 9 , 12 , ..... what should come next ?",
  option: [
  "7",
  "10",
  "11",
  "13",
  ],
  answer: 2, 
},
{
  question: "Look at the this series : 36 , 34 , 30 , 28 , 24 , .... what should come next ?",
  option: [
  "20",
  "23",
  "18",
  "22",
  ],
  answer: 4, 
},
{
  question: "Look at the series : 31 , 29 , 24 , 22 , 17 , .... what should come next ?",
  option: [
  "15",
  "14",
  "13",
  "12",
  ],
  answer: 1, 
},
{
  question: "2 is a :",
  option: [
  "Prime number",
  "Composite number",
  "Neither Prime nor Composite ",
  "Odd number ",
  ],
  answer: 1, 
},
    ]   
